我要正式抗议一次
I want to register a formal protest.
知道了
Noted.
你考虑周全了吗
Have you thought of everything?
当然没有
Course not.
没必要考虑自取灭亡的事
It doesn't occur to me how to engineer my own destruction.
我们这样穿过了密苏里河
We crossed the Missouri like this,
那条河比克劳河更宽广
greater river than the Crow.
那时冰更厚  天更冷
Thicker ice, colder weather.
而且我比火车司机更大胆
And larger balls than my chief engineer.
你说了算
You're the boss.
谁拿着钱
Who holdin' the money?
-大家都加入吗  -是啊
- Everybody in? - Uh-huh.
那个谁  大块头
You there, big fella.
人们叫我帕萨姆  杜兰特先生
They call me Psalms, Mr. Durant.
帕萨姆  当然啦
Psalms, yes, of course, Psalms.
赌注是什么
What's the wager?
火车司机过多久会跳车
How far across before the engineer jump.
你觉得火车过不去吗
You don't think the train's gonna make it?
我赌的不是铁路
I ain't bettin' against the railroad itself,
杜兰特先生  只是火车司机
Mr. Durant, just the engineer.
当然啦
Of course.
火车司机  开车过河
Engineer, take it across.
恭喜  杜兰特先生
Congratulations, Mr. Durant.
锅炉烧得火红  车轮飞速旋转
Red hot boiler on ice, wheels spinning.
不掉到冰里才怪
What'd you think was gonna happen?
地狱之轮
第四季  第一集
四
之
水很甜
Water is sweet and good.
如果你们现在被印第安人袭击或放火
You get attacked by Indians now or set fire to,
就不用去河边取水了
won't have to go down to the river.
万一你不在时被袭击了呢
You'll not be here, should that happen?
我向你保证
Gave you my word,
我会等到庄稼长好  孩子生了再走
I'd be here till the crops is in, baby's born.
娜奥米随时都可能生
Naomi's due any day now.
之后唯一让我留在这里的就是达森主教
Only thing keeping me here after that'll be Bishop Dutson.
你对我遵守了承诺
Well, you have honored your word to me.
毫无疑问  他也会感觉如此
No doubt, he'll feel the same.
我要是走出门  他就会给我背上来一枪
I try to walk out that gate, he'll put a bullet in my back.
达森主教不是你说的那种人
Bishop Dutson is not the man you claim him to be.
海彻神父  我一直告诉你
Father Hatch, I keep telling you,
他不是他自称的那种人
he ain't the man he claims to be.
骗子绝对不会像达森主教那样
An imposter could never lay on hands
进行圣疗  讲灵言
and speak in tongues like Bishop Dutson.
是啊
Yeah.
总有一天你会知道的
One day you'll see.
关门
Close the gate!
-博汉南兄弟  -夏安镇怎么样
- Brother Bohannon. - How's Cheyenne?
一切安好
Sodom and Gomorrah's got nothing on it.
铁路又开始修了吗
Railroad started stockpiling rail yet?
遇到麻烦停工了  不过我听说
Railroad's stuck and busted. I did hear
骑兵队击溃了科曼奇人
the cavalry's got the Comanche on the run, though.
下次注意不要剪头发
Mind you don't get a haircut next time.
也没多少好剪的了
Slim pickings.
那口新井挖得不错啊
Wonderful work on the new well.
小心别掉下去了
Careful you don't fall in.
尽量在高墙之内享受上帝赐予的宁静
Oh, try to enjoy God's peace within these walls.
这里这么漂亮
Fort this pretty,
我都快忘记自己是个囚犯了
it's hard to remember I'm a prison.
你是自由之人  博汉南兄弟
You are a free man, Brother Bohannon.
可以自由离开吗
Free to leave, you mean?
看到他们用拳头打架太好了
It's good to see the men fight with their fists.
通常他们会动刀子动枪的
Usually, they reach right for their knives and guns.
在河里损失的材料设备
It's the final tally for the material
都清点好了
lost in the river.
我手头没这么多钱
I don't have this kind of money on hand.
去弄  否则中太平洋公司的人会来...
Find it, or the Central Pacific will meet us here...
这个天杀的地方见我们
in this God forsaken place.
我看你妻子在这里不开心啊
Your wife is unhappy here, I take it.
她父亲是你的挚友
Her father was one of your best friends.
人失踪了你却无动于衷
He goes missing, you do nothing about it.
胡说  我们各处都找遍了
Well, at's not true. We looked everywhere.
我们真的该找时间一起吃个饭
You know, we really should have dinner sometime,
重新了解一下彼此  我可以向她解释
so we can reacquaint. I can explain it to her.
她肯定愿意
Oh, she'd love that,
因为她还担心你跟她父亲的失踪
since she worries you had something to do
有什么关系
with his disappearance.
是谁让她有这种
Who could possibly have put such a hairbrained idea
-愚蠢的想法的  -一个波士顿来的警探
- in her head? - A Boston detective.
就是去年来的那个
The one who came out here last year.
她父亲梅特卡夫议员
Her father, senator Metcalf,
是我多年的挚友
was one of my oldest and closest friends.
天呐  我是她的教父
I was her godfather, for Christ's sakes!
所以她才如此害怕
Well, that's what makes it so frightening for her.
我会尽可能回答她的问题
I will do everything I can to answer her questions.
同时你记得提醒你妻子谨慎小心
Meanwhile, advise your wife to be cautious.
夏安镇是个危险的地方
Cheyenne is a dangerous place.
伊娃
Eva?
你好  杜兰特先生
Howdy, Mr. Durant.
伊娃  你肯定可以
Eva, surely, you can find
找到比帮妓女洗被褥更合适的工作
something more suitable than washing whores' bedding.
米奇好心给我工作
Well, Mickey was good to give me the work.
不做这个我就得去做妓女
It's either this or go back to whoring.
看着我  伊娃
Look at me, Eva.
当我在破产边缘时
The eyes of the world are upon me,
全世界都无动于衷
as I stand on the verge of ruin.
四面楚歌  我妻子在我进监狱时
Harassed on all sides, my wife left me
离开了我  我没有朋友
while I was in prison, I have no friends,
但是你没看到我哭对吧
but you don't see me crying, do you?
我没哭  所以你要振作起来
No, so pick yourself up.
是  杜兰特先生
Yes, Mr. Durant.
很好
Good.
镇长先生
Mr. Mayor.
我有事相商
I am seeking counsel.
乐意为我的选民效劳
Always happy to oblige one of my constituents.
铁路破产了
Ahh. The railroad is broke.
换做是你  你会怎么做
If you were me, what would you do?
先生  根据以往经验  你肯定会回东部
Historically, sir, you'd have gone back east
靠兜售假文书敛财数百万
And sold a bunch of phony paper for millions of dollars,
但是弄沉火车之后
But after sinking the train,
你的信誉恐怕大不如前了
I'd say you have credibility concerns.
没错  换做你会怎么做
Correct, so what would you do now?
把值钱的资产悉数抛售
Sell off anything you have of value,
这块怀表也不例外
including that watch.
我出价五美元
I'll give you a fiver for it.
我手上还有地  铁路两边各20英亩
I have land, 20 acres either side of the track,
以及开采权归我所有的其他地皮
and any land I can claim mineral rights to.
你应该把那些地  全拍卖掉
You should sell it... at auction.
而你  应该把那些地都买下来
And you should buy it, at auction.
我不想买
I don't want it,
我也不想惹上麻烦
And I don't want that kind of trouble.
我把你送上镇长宝座  让你盆满钵盈
I made you mayor. I made you rich.
你乍到时还是个只会傻笑的戏法匠
You arrived with a magic show and a dopey smile.
我可以让你走时的境况更惨
You could leave with a lot less.
给我发个告示  弄得正规点儿
Post a notice, something official.
还有  带够现钱
Oh, and bring cash.
还有  看在上帝的份上  拉伊娃一把
And for god sakes, get Eva out of the mud.
有些人偏喜欢身陷泥潭不愿人帮忙
Some people don't want to be pulled out of the mud,
杜兰特先生
Mr. Durant.
没错
True.
千万别当那种傻子
Don't be one of them.
来
Here.
看看报纸吧
Go ahead and read it.
冬天之后铁路施工落下了不少
Your railroad's fallen behind during the winter.
杜兰特有列火车沉到克劳河里去了
Durant sunk a train into the Crow River
还说只是小麻烦
and called it a minor setback, so...
他遇到了麻烦  可能因为没有你帮忙
He struggles, probably 'cause you're not there.
总工程师马丁·德兰尼今天说
"Chief engineer Martin Delaney announced today."
混帐  真不敢相信
Damn it! I can't believe this.
怎么了
What is it?
真想不到
I can't believe
杜兰特还没炒了马丁·德兰尼那个白痴
Durant hadn't fired that idiot Martin Delaney by now.
我已经撵走他一次了
I beat him out for the job once already.
我知道那项铁路工程对你多重要
I know how much that railroad means to you.
你是来修铁路的
You came out here to build it,
而不是跟一个你可能压根就不爱的妻子
Not live a life among people who aren't your own,
生活在一群不相干的人中
with a wife that you may not love.
我来到铁路上
Come to the railroad huntin'...
是为了找到谋杀我妻儿的凶手
the men who murdered my wife and child.
能找到的都被我手刃了
Killed the ones I could find.
所以  娜奥米
Now, Naomi...
你的老公是个杀人犯
You're married to a killer.
你只是想让我害怕到不敢爱你
You're just tryin' to scare me into not lovin' you
然后离开这里
so you can leave.
不  我只是实话实说
No, I'm just bein' truthful is all.
放心走吧  卡伦
You can leave, Cullen.
我不会有事儿的
I'll be all right.
夏安报
谢谢
Thank you.
很不错
It's quite all right.
吃面包吗  丈夫
Bread, husband?
为什么不坐下来  休息一下
Why don't you have a seat? Rest a spell.
就像这样
There you go.
我很高兴
Well, I'm glad.
跟我们相处了四个月  你终于有了朋友
After four months among us, you're making friends.
只有一个朋友
I can count 'em all on one finger.
杜特利兄弟呢
Brother Dultey.
会你来我往的说几句话
I talk to him, he talks to me.
他从夏安镇回来之后尤甚
Especially when he returns from his trips to Cheyenne.
忘了夏安镇吧  都是过去的事了
Let go of Cheyenne, your former life.
我想和你说点事  主教
I want to talk to you about something, bishop.
什么事
Yes?
你之前说过的关于自由的事
That thing you said about freedom earlier.
我觉得我终于明白了
I think I finally understand it.
很好
Good. Good!
-还有别的  -什么
- And--and something else. - Mm-hmm?
我看到了神启幻象
I had me a vision.
说来听听
Tell me.
在幻象中我离开了这个地方
I had me a vision that I was leaving this place.
为什么呢
But why?
这里还有...很多你未完成的事情
Th-there's still... so much to be done with you.
我不知道  我只是...
I don't know, I just...
看见自己径直走过了那扇门
Saw myself walkin' straight through that gate.
南北战争时南方邦联的国歌
-不  -径直穿过了那扇门  吹着《迪克西》
- No, no. - Walkin' right out through that gate, whistling Dixie.
你不能抛弃你的妻儿
You--you would not abandon your wife and child.
是的
Yeah.
不用担心
I wouldn't worry none.
只是幻象而已
It's just a vision.
坎贝尔先生  格兰特将军可以见你了
Mr. Campbell, General Grant will see you now.
格兰特将军
General Grant.
我已当选  我要把你派到西部  坎贝尔
With my election assured, I'm sending you west, Campbell.
怀俄明  听说过吗
Wyoming. Ever hear of it?
-略有耳闻  -无法无天的地方
- Vaguely. - Lawless place.
联合太平洋公司已经深陷其中
Union Pacific has gotten itself bogged down out there.
那里现在一片混乱
Things are running amok.
我不认为我是去那里的合适人选
I don't think I'm the man you want to send there.
你不会回到亚特兰大的
You will not be returning to Atlanta.
我在那里的工作还没有结束
My work there is incomplete.
我这是为你好  坎贝尔
I'm saving you from yourself, campbell.
你做得有点过了
You were a bit overzealous.
错误已经铸成  但秩序也恢复了
Mistakes were made, but order was restored.
希望你当怀俄明临时州长时也能如此
And you'll do the same as the provisional governor of wyoming.
好运  先生
Good luck, sir.
将军  很荣幸得到这个机会
General, you honor me with this opportunity.
混乱的街头  夏安镇陷入动荡和无序
功利主义名言  提倡不择手段达到福利最大化
为最多的人
The greatest good
谋求最大的幸福是我们的目标
to the greatest number is the object to attain.
这需要人和财产的安全
This requires security of person and property in every--
先生们  将军对我们在
Gentlemen, the general is very pleased
亚特兰大的成功非常满意
with our success in Atlanta.
他不会免去我们的职务吗
He's not giving us the boot?
恰恰相反
On the contrary,
他任命我管理一块新领地
he appointed me governor of a new territory.
-哪一个  -怀俄明
- Which one? - Wyoming.
-没听说过  -尚待开发的边疆
- Never heard of it. - The frontier.
那是荒蛮之地
It's a wilderness.
这比被免职还惨
This is worse than getting the boot.
别这么快下结论  西部有黄金
Well, not so fast. There's gold out west.
自由之地
Free land out here,
对于有远见的人来说机会大把
opportunities for those with a keen eye.
那里不是汪洋大盗肆虐的地盘
This is not a place of hooded rascals,
废墟之城
a city in ashes.
那里确实很荒芜  但也百废待兴
It's wild, surely, but so is an unbroken horse.
我们将推倒废墟
We'll break it.
你会成为整个领地的临时治安官
You'll be provisional marshal of the whole territory.
你会是法官
You'll be the judge.
你会是财政部长
You'll be the treasurer.
这些都是格兰特说的吗
Grant says all this?
收拾行李  别拿显眼的毛毡包
Pack your gear. No carpet bags.
怀俄明
Wyoming.
早上好  先生们
Good morning, gentlemen.
今早你们有难得的机会
This morning, you have a rare opportunity
购买一些很有价值的土地
to buy some very valuable land.
谁有兴趣拍下山谷北侧的二十一号土地
Now, what bid do I hear for parcel 21 in the North Valley?
我真不想卖这块心头肉
It breaks my heart to offer it.
我们也不想买  那里是自由放养区
Ours too. It's open range.
万一有人圈占了怎么办
What if somebody fences it in?
正如你说的  那片自由放养区
That open range, as you call it,
是联合太平洋铁路公司授权的
was granted by the largess of the Union Pacific Railroad.
四百美元
$400.
五百美元
$500.
五百美元  出价是五百美元  先生们
$500. The bid is $500, gentlemen.
有没有更高的
And the advance?
五百零一美元
$501.
五百零一美元  一次  两次
$501. Going once, going twice...
六百美元
$600.
帕默夫人
Mrs. Palmer.
这是在干什么  托马斯
Just what is this stunt, Thomas?
这是拍卖会  玛吉
This is an auction, Maggie.
我看到了
Hmm, I see that.
我以为对联太铁路公司的土地咱们有过协议
I thought we had an agreement about the use of this U.P. Land
要作为自由放养区
for free range.
是的  不管是谁赢得拍卖  也许你可以
Yes, and perhaps you can strike a similar deal with the new owner,
和那位新地主达成协议
whomever that may be.
我已经和你达成了协议  杜兰特  永久的
I struck a deal with you, Durant, in perpetuity.
而你却跟你的走狗违反了协议
Now, you're reneging behind your flunky here.
我不是走狗  我是夏安镇的镇长
I'm not a flunky. I'm the mayor of Cheyenne.
你要是想挑起牧区战争
If you're looking for a range war,
只要说声"拉铁丝网"就行
just say, "Barbed wire".
我想要的是六百美元拍卖金
I'm looking at a bid of $600.
六百零一美元
$601.
一千
$1,000.
一千零一
$1,001.
两千
$2,000.
我要破坏你的阴谋
I'm going to ruin this scheme.
两千零一
$2,001?
三千
$3,000.
下面的  你好啊
Hello, down there!
把梯子放下来  主教
Drop down that ladder, bishop.
博汉南兄弟  我已经考虑过
Brother Bohannon, I've been contemplating
你预见自己要离开我们的事了
your vision to leave us.
还记得你最后一次不得不在暴力中
When was the last time you had to draw a gun
拔枪  或动手吗
or raise a hand in violence?
现在的生活不是充满平静吗
Isn't there a peace in that?
我原本期待把洞挖深
I was hoping digging this hole into the earth
能给予你深思熟虑的时间
would give you time to contemplate your soul,
可以提醒你
A daily reminder of...
我们对回归光明的需求
of our need to return to the light.
上帝让我降临人间拯救你的灵魂  博汉南兄弟
God has put me on earth to save your soul, brother Bohannon.
我知道你对那深信不疑
I believe you believe that.
不要拒绝第二次机会
Don't say no to this second chance.
年轻漂亮的妻子  还有宝贝儿子
Beautiful young wife and precious son,
我们交谈时他也许正要呱呱坠地
whose arrival may be heralded as we speak.
给我梯子
The ladder.
上帝已经告诉我她会生男孩  知道吗
God has spoken to me that it is a boy, you know?
-卡伦  -把梯子放下来
- Cullen! - Drop down that ladder.
利用这段时间思考一下我们的谈话吧
Will you use this time to meditate on these words?
卡伦  卡伦
Cullen! Cullen!
把梯子放下来
Throw down that ladder!
-卡伦  -主教
- Cullen! - Ugh! Bishop!
卡伦
Cullen!
主教
Bishop!
主教问我你离开的事
Bishop asked me about your leaving.
是吗  你怎么说
Yeah? What'd you tell him?
什么都没说  我以为你喜欢这里
Nothin', I thought you liked it here.
不  我们必须在外面等
No, we wait.
见鬼去吧
To hell with that.
卡伦  求你了
Cullen, please!
你也这样
You too?
别让那个狗娘养的靠近我妻子
I don't want that sumbitch anywhere near my wife.
分娩出现了点困难
There seems to be a difficulty in the birthing.
她恳求那个异教徒进来
She's begging for the gentile.
卡伦
Cullen!
让我上去
Let me go.
求你们了
Please?
卡伦  求求你
oh, Cullen, please!
我来了  我来了  来了
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
没事的
It's okay.
你得把孩子转过来
You're gonna have to turn the baby.
我们正在努力
We're doing that.
那就再快一点
Do it faster.
我们已经尽全力了
We're doing the best we can.
她年轻又健康
She's young, healthy.
我第一任妻子也年轻健康
My first wife was young and healthy,
但我们失去了一对双胞胎
and we lost twins.
快一点
Do it.
没事的
It's all right.
不会有事的
你让我成了玛吉·帕莫和那群牧民的仇人
And you made me an enemy of Maggie Palmer and her cattlemen.
准确地说是一群赶牛的乡巴佬
Shitkickers and cow-punchers.
她说我是你的走狗
She called me your flunky.
大餐里总会有沙子
Ah, the grit in your oyster.
麦克吉尼斯先生  你是夏安镇的镇长
Mr. Mcginnes, you are the mayor of Cheyenne,
现在还是整个怀俄明州
and now, the second largest property owner
第二大的产权人
in the entire Wyoming territory.
你把我榨干了
You wiped me out.
我只是把钱从一个账转到了另一个账上
Merely transferring money from one ledger to another.
谢谢
Thank you.
走狗  不对
Ah. Flunky, no.
合伙人  正确
Partner, yes.
你和你弟弟不同  迈克尔
You are not your brother, Michael.
为我祈祷
Pray for me.
*珍贵的孩子还未诞生*
*Precious babe you remain foretold*
求你了
Please?
*自灵而生*
*Born of spirit*
我们在天上的父
Our father, who art in heaven.
该死  我忘了后面的
Shit, forgot the rest of it.
*保佑这位母亲*
*Bless this mother*
愿人都尊你的名为圣
Hallowed be thy name.
愿你的国降临
Thy kingdom come,
愿你的旨意
Thy will be done...
行在地上
On earth...
请饶恕我们的过犯
And forgive us our trespasses,
就像我们饶恕他人的过犯一样
as we forgive those who trespass against us.
粗心的婊子
Careless bitch.
看看你干的好事
Look what you've done.
泥浆让你好看点了
Mud'd be an improvement to you.
作为一家之主
As head of the family,
你该第一个抱他
you should be the first to hold him.
祝福你  达森主教
Bless you, Bishop Dutson,
用你的祈祷拯救了我们
for saving us with your prayers.
上帝  保佑这孩子
Lord God, bless this child,
你的  我的  我们的
Yours, mine, ours.
直至永远  阿门
Forever and ever, amen.
也祝福你  我的孩子
And bless you, my children.
祂的旨意必被奉行
God's will be done.
发电报给奥马哈  运铁轨和枕木来
Wire Omaha to ship rail and ties.
这是新的银行账
That's the new bank ledger.
这是给你的
This came for you.
格兰特将军发来的机密电报
Confidential, from General Grant.
有人来陪你了
You got company comin',
新任的怀俄明临时州长
new provisional Governor of Wyoming.
"约翰·坎贝尔及手下"
"John Campbell and staff."
你要好好招待  尽力帮助坎贝尔
You're to show Campbell every courtesy and assistance.
别过分  德莱尼
Don't overstep, Delaney.
格兰特将军向我和我夫人问好
General Grant sends his best to me and Mrs. Delaney.
先是我自己的公司派你来监视我
First, my own company sends you to spy on me,
现在  政府又派来个监工
and now, the government sends an overseer.
谁都知道你有多大本事
Everyone knows what you're capable of.
识相点  你个狗杂碎
Steady, you son of a bitch!
我本事通天
I am capable of anything,
你妻子就很清楚
as your wife so clearly intuits.
我从没说过杀她父亲不是好主意
I never said killing her father was a bad idea.
你父亲叫什么
What was your father's name?
威廉  威廉·埃德加
William. William Edgar.
威廉
William.
你喜欢他吗
Did you like him?
比小时候喜欢
I like him better the older I get.
北方佬枪杀了他
Yankees shot him.
我们叫他威廉吧
Let's name him William.
我喜欢这名字
I like it.
我们要一起离开这里
We're leaving here together,
你  我和小威廉
you, me, and baby William,
但走之前  你谁都别告诉
But you can't tell nobody till right before we go,
明白吗
you understand?
你想带我...  带我们一起吗
You want me? Y- you want us?
是的
Yes.
你吊死我儿子以后  答应我丈夫
You promised my husband a life for a life
一命换一命
after you hung my son.
事情没这么简单
There's more to it than that.
对  没这么简单
Yes, there is.
每次我看到你  想到的只有杰布
Every time I see you, all I can think about is my Jeb
吊在你手里可怕的套索上
swinging from that horrible noose at your hand.
对不起  海彻夫人
I'm sorry, Mother Hatch.
我要的...不是你的歉意
It's not your-- your sorrow,
你的同情
your pity I want.
我要你离开这里
I want you to leave this place.
看到你我就恶心  别人也是
The sight of you sickens me, as it does others.
娜奥米会把这孩子当弟弟抚养
Naomi will raise the child as her brother.
他的名字要叫杰布达亚·海彻
His name shall be Jebediah Hatch.
最后  你会被遗忘
In time, you will be forgotten.
娜奥米年轻健康  她会活得比自己丈夫久
Naomi is young and healthy and will outlive her husbands,
延续我们的传统
as is our custom...
从你离开以后开始
beginning with you.
天呐
Jesus.
过来吧
Get over here.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我为你尽力了  伊娃
I've done all I can for you, Eva.
我给了你两次离开这里的车费
Twice I gave you train fare out of this place,
而你依然没有离开
And you still don't leave.
这个世界没有我的容身之处  米奇
There's no place for me in this world, Mickey.
这都是你自找的
You bring it all on yourself.
你跟黑鬼厮混
You involved yourself with a...Negro.
我爱埃兰
I loved Elam.
你要是真爱他
You loved him so much
怎么会送走他深爱的孩子
that you gave away the baby that he adored.
这不对
That ain't right.
你就不该放弃卖身
You should never have left off the whoring.
这行你最拿手
You were good at that.
与生俱来
A natural.
所有女人生来都是妓女
All women are whores by nature...
除了我妈以外
I suppose except for me mum.
这是女人唯一的共同点
It's the one thing that all women have in common.
她们只会卖
Whoring.
她们只是妓女
Just whores.
归根结底
At the end of the day...
她们都是妓女
They're all whores.
你现在满意了吗
Is everything where you thought it would be?
什么
What?
我说  你现在满意了吗
I said, "Is everything where you thought it would be?"
我
I--
我没有...
I wouldn't--
我不是有意的
Didn't mean to.
玛吉  加入我吧
Maggie! Join me.
在今天之前我还挺喜欢你的
I actually liked you until today.
你依然喜欢我
Oh, you still like me.
你只是不信任我  这非常正常
You just don't trust me. That's perfectly normal.
我必须那样做  玛吉  我需要钱
I had to do it, Maggie. I needed the money.
所以你现在独坐于此  带着你的钱
So here you sit with your money, alone.
我在等待领地的新州长
I'm expecting the new governor of the territory.
他的火车晚点了
His train is late.
总有一天  当你需要信任之人时
One day, you will need someone that you can trust.
你只会找到一整屋的空椅子
All you'll find is a room of...Empty chairs.
我也有那样的包
I have bags just like those.
这些是你的包
Oh, those are your bags,
这是你的账单
And here is your bill.
账单
Bill?
我猜你会来威胁我
Figured you'd bring the threat.
我是来讲和的
A plea.
你嘴里的话总是真假难辨
Well, things can be two at once in your mouth.
你直接杀了我
You kill me outright,
人们就会看到你的本来面目
you'll be seen for what you are.
我直接杀了你
Hmm. I kill you outright,
你就会变成某种圣人  而我会被吊死
You'd be some kind of saint, and I'd hang.
一旦你踏出这扇门
Once outside those gates,
我就不能保证你的安全
I cannot guarantee your safety.
我们的安全  我要带家人一起走
Our safety. Taking my family with me.
你的家人
Your family?
没错
That's right.
你不允许我离开
You not allowing me to leave...
做这决定是达森主教
Is that as Bishop Dutson,
还是瑞典佬  或者说托尔·刚德森
Or as the Swede, also known as Thor Gundersen?
过世的托尔·刚德森是挪威人
The late Thor Gundersen was Norwegian.
那么
Well...
不管你是谁
Whoever you are...
你最好瞄准点
You better shoot to kill.
因为我会回来了结一切恩怨
I'm coming back to finish this once and for all.